TRAN QUANG MINH

Ho Chi Minh City * mtran8@binghamton.edu * 0933061291 Github: https://github.com/minhtran612 Online CV:https://my-resume-personal.herokuapp.com

SUMMARY:

I had a Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering but for the most part of my career I worked as a Software Developer. I mainly used C/C++ to program embedded applications. Recently, I decided to teach myself the web technology and I felt in love with JavaScript. I found that this field has a ton of interesting things to discover. I set my goal to be a full stack developer in the next 5 years that can work well in frontend, backend. Fervent believer that experiences and challenges will make me a stronger programmer.

EXPERIENCE:

Embedded Software Engineer

3/2015 - 10/2015

Renesas Design Vietnam

Work on a team to build the profiler for the internal graphic API. This profiler software measures the performance of the rendering ability in both hardware and software mode.

Embedded Software Engineer

12/2015 - 1/2017

Wirecard Vietnam

Develop and maintain the applications and firmware for the POS (Point of Sale) for most of the banks in Vietnam. I was also in charge of developing new features for Payoo (Vietnam) and Reddot (Myanmar) - applications on POS for merchant to collect utility bills.

SKILLS:

General: embedded software such as firmware for various kind of hardware, including sensors, motors...etc. Developing web application with knowledge on React framework, NodeJS.

Programming Languages: C, JavaScript and Python. **Languages:** Native Vietnamese, proficient at English.

EDUCATION:

International University of VNU

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering 2009 –2012

GPA: 3.5 (4 point system)

State University of New York at Binghamton 2012- 2014

Bachelor of Science, Electrical Engineering

GPA: 3.33 (4 point system)